Finding Aid for the Lloyd Bochner Scripts PASC.0116
UCLA Library Special Collections
- MINISERIES
  - LOUISIANA (1984)
    - [THEATRICAL SCRIPT]. Script dated 3/1/83. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - PART I, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - PART II, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - PART III, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 7)
- RADIO
  - CBS RADIO MYSTERY THEATRE
    - INTANGIBLES, THE. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - MUTUAL RADIO THEATER: THE ADVENTURE SHOW
    - NEARLY PERFECT CRIME, A. Script dated 2/29/80. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - MUTUAL RADIO THEATER: THE LOVE SHOW
    - MR. HANLEY DRINKS TOO MUCH CHAMPAGNE. Script dated 3/21/80. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - SEARS RADIO THEATER
    - MERCENARIES, THE. Script dated 2/2/79. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - SEARS RADIO THEATER: THE ADVENTURE SHOW
    - SHAH-NAMA. Script dated 3/16/79. (Box 24, Folder 3)
- TELEVISION SPECIAL
  - REX HARRISON PRES. SHORT STORIES OF LOVE
    - FORTUNATE PAINTER, THE. Script dated 12/10/71. (Box 25, Folder 6)
- MADE FOR TELEVISION MOVIES
  - COLLISION COURSE (1975)
    - Script dated 11/5/75. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - CROWHAVEN FARM (1970)
    - Script dated 7/13/70. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - DOUBLE AGENT (1987)
    - Script dated 12/12/86. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - FIRE IN THE SKY, A (1978)
    - Script dated 12/23/77. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - GOLDEN GATE MURDERS, THE (1979)
    - Script dated 1/4/79. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - HOUND OF THE BASKERVILLES, THE (1972)
    - Script dated 12/13/71. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - RONA JAFFE'S "MAZES AND MONSTERS" (1982)
    - Script dated 9/12/82. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - SATAN'S SCHOOL FOR GIRLS (1973)
    - Script dated 6/1/73. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - STRANGERS ON THE RUN (1967)
    - Script dated 8/10/66. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - TERRACES (1977)
    - Script dated 2/7/77. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - THEY CALL IT MURDER (1971)
    - Script dated 9/25/69. (Box 24, Folder 8)
- MISCELLANEOUS SCRIPTS
  - CODE BLUE AFFAIR, THE
    - Script dated 10/27/78. Writer(s): OBROW, JEFFREY D. - * CARPENTER, STEPHEN W. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - CROSS COUNTRY
    - Script dated 4/13/82. Writer(s): HUNTER, JOHN - * KASTLE, HERBERT (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - DICK FRANCIS MYSTERIES
    - EPISODE # 01 - BLOODSPORT. Script dated 6/22/89. Writer(s): PAYNE, ANDREW (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - FIND THE LADY
    - Script dated 9/1/75. Writer(s): MAIN, DAVID - * TRENT, JOHN (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - JERICHO
    - unspecified (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - LOON ISLAND
    - Writer(s): HUME, CYRIL - * MAIBAUM, RICHARD (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - LORD GRIZZLY [SYNOPSIS]
    - Writer(s): MANFRED, FREDERICK F. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - PUSHERS DIE HARD
    - Writer(s): COWDEN, JACK (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - RACE TO THE BOMB, THE
    - EPISODE ONE. Script dated 11/25/85. Writer(s): DELASSUS, JEAN-FRANCOIS - * FORSYTH, ROB - * SHEER, TONY (Box 27, Folder 6)